Heiwa Fansubs Presents:
"Great Detective Conan"
Challenge to Kudo Shin'ichi
Oh! It's that case!
That wedding-party case
I settled at a crack!
Ah, the one where it was
your fault someone died.
The case of the party where
you got overly excited...
...and, thanks to that,
gave an opening for someone to be killed.
You're giving me a bad reputation!
That was the case where...
...after you had forced the bride and groom
to kiss one another, someone died, isn't it?
Foolishness!
Ran, I was trying to protect your
precious boy here's First Kiss.
Kiss?
He's wrong, wrong, wrong.
Hmm... What's this about?
Wait and I'll tell you!
How do I put this...
It was your fault it happened.
Eh?
"Kensuke - Kanon
Congratulations on Your Marriage"
Are you serious?
Yes.
What'll we do?
"What'll we do," you ask...
I'm getting married today.
I won't let you off easy.
I've got my pride.
"Bridegroom, 'Diavel's Kiss' Manager
Motoki Kensuke"
Even if you say that...
I'll be expecting a more solid answer.
By the end of the day.
"Bride
Shimabara Kanon"
Whaa! So beautiful!
Congratulations on your wedding.
Thank you.
Nana...
Is something happening between
you and Kei-chan?
Stop it.
There's no way anything could happen between
your best friend and the one you're marrying.
You and I are friends.
Motoki-san's a friend, too.
That's all.
I see...
- Sorry if I said anything weird.
- No.
- Then, see you later.
- Later.
Ah, but Kanon.
"Friend of the Bride
Masumoto Nana"
I won't be me, but if something does happen,
it won't be my responsibility.
Eh?
If such a thing happened,
I might have to kill you two.
Whaa... scary.
Penalty game?
What's that?
You had a brain lock
at lunch, didn't you?
You said you'd play a penalty game
if you lost, didn't you?
- Kudo-kun, you lost, didn't you?
- You lost, you lost!
You guys won by cheating.
It wasn't cheating.
It was strategy.
- Right?
Nothing I can do.
And?
Shin'ichi can't turn down any favors
from anyone for the entire day.
"Shin'ichi's Childhood Friend
Mori Ran"
Since this is a penalty game,
make sure you do it right.
- Here, take this.
- Yes, yes, I've got it.
"Shin'ichi and Ran's Fellow Student
Suzuki Sonoko"
Then from here you can treat me
at a family restaurant...
Yes?
Sir?
Eh? You need a favor?
Kyaa! He's really come!
It's the real Shin'ichi-kun!
"Friend of Bride: Niizuma Ayaka
Friend of the Bride: Onna Yuka"
"Why are these girls
dressed up so flashily for?"
"Private Detective
Mori Kogoro"
Girls...
Don't forget the one who called for this foremost
high school detective, Kudo Shin'ichi-kun...
...was I, the super-great detective,
Mori Kogoro!
Sir, what's this
"deep-cover investigation" about?
A wedding.
Huh?!
All of these kittens are regular customers
here at "Diavel's Kiss."
And the Master of the place and his
regular customer Kanon-chan are getting married.
So they asked me to arrange
and hold this party for them.
Take care of these right away.
As a favor.
Eh?! Another favor...
That Nana...
"What'll we do," she asks.
I'm hungry.
Ken-chan, don't you have anything?
We're having the party right now.
You want to eat before that?
But I can't just stuff my face
in front of everyone wearing this, can I?
I'll have to starve until I'm a bride.
Ah, this'll do fine.
That's yesterday's leftovers.
It's okay, it's okay.
Oi, that's my secret ingredient;
if you put that in, it'll taste bad.
I know...
Ken-chan's "Final Curry" is delicious.
Excuse me.
Yes, I'm in your debt.
Yeah, yes.
Excuse me.
It really is Kudo-kun.
Incredible!
Could I ask you to sign this?
Ah, thanks for your hard work.
Ah, that's right, Kudo-kun.
Could I ask a favor of you?
Ah, heavy!
I'm being run around like a slave.
I can't. I just can't.
You just can't?
Then, I guess I'll have to give birth.
Eh?
Because I don't want to
cause you trouble, Motoki-kun.
Seems heavy for them, too.
Think I'll take a detour.
Ken-chan, something happen?
Eh? Ah, it was nothing.
Just work.
Ken-chan, truth is,
I need to say I'm sorry to you.
Eh?
I've been suspicious of you and Nana lately.
The two of you have
been meeting, haven't you?
Ah...
Look, it was about that.
Nana-chan's business.
She's looking to buy health foods.
That's it!
She's decided to do that, has she?
Yet I thought something was going on.
I'm sorry.
Not at all.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
Could it be you were about to kiss just now...
Ah, I caught you right in the middle of it.
No...
I had no intention of bothering you,
but I ended up doing something boorish.
Ah! Ah! Curry! Curry!
What'll we do?
Thanks for waiting!
The entrance of the Bride and Groom!
Cue! Cue!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Set the night on fire!
Brush your teeth!
Sir, what's with this stain?
I got some curry on it.
You some school kid?
Excuse me. Telegram.
Thanks.
Big round of applause.
Please give them a big round of applause!
"If you have an affair, I'll kill you"
"I'll kill you"
A photo, a photo.
Look this way, look this way.
To your left, your left!
Say cheese!
Ehh... well then, on the occasion of
Motoki Kensuke-san...
...and the soon to be Motoki Kanon-san...
...but currently Shimabara Kanon-san's wedding.
Kanpai!
- Kanpai!
You could say the start
of these two being together...
...came after Kanon-san had eaten
the "Final Curry"...
...that the bridegroom had made for her
and she became addicted to it.
Well, long ago when
Tokugawa Ieyasu was alive...
Sir!
People hate long speeches.
Eh... Well then, it's presumptuous of me...
...but I, Mori Kogoro, will now read out
the congratulatory telegrams.
"Congratulations on your marriage!"
"Be happy for eternity!
From Michiko."
That's pretty ordinary, isn't it?
It's ordinary, I'd say.
This one doesn't have a sender!
This one'll be a big hit!
"If you have an affair, I'll kill you!"
Ah, ala?
Something wrong?
Eh? What's that?
That's a seriously
super-popular thing to do.
Well then, um...
so much for the telegrams.
So that there are no worries at all
about these two cheating on one another...
...let's have them kiss!
Eh?
Well, don't ask us for that!
That's embarrassing!
A kiss is an indispensible part of a wedding!
Kiss, kiss, kiss...
Don't let it die down!
Make 'em do it!
Kiss! Kiss!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
I'm vexed at their happiness!
Let's really get drunk today!
Right!
Okay! All of today's dishes were homemade
by the bridegroom himself!
Yeah!
"If you have an affair, I'll kill you"
He also personally shook the shaker
and made all the cocktails!
"Let's hope this telegram
is nothing but a prank."
Say, Shin'ichi-kun.
Touch my cheeks.
Eh?!
Will you touch my cheeks?
If not my cheeks,
then will you touch some other place?
Say, say, touch me.
Ah! Miss, are you okay?
Ah!
You're staring at her breasts!
I'm not!
What? What, what!?
Hey, boy detective!
It's still way too early for you
to be investigating that!
I'll take over from here.
Kogoro-chan, rather than that,
go talk to Nana.
Abandoning this drunk young lady
would be irresponsible of me, now wouldn't it?
I'll sober you up.
Now, now.
Are you okay!?
Are you okay, Yuka-chan?!
Hey!
Kogoro!
Are you jumping ship for Yuka?
Nana-chaaan!
You're the most beautiful one in the world!
Then, buy me some
alligator juice this time.
Let's have some alligator juice with gusto!
(Gusto = Mori Mori)
The bridegroom's very popular, isn't he?
That's true.
Because he's so handsome, isn't he?
Even I wanted to date him...
"Looks like that telegram
was nothing more than a prank."
I should have just pushed myself onto him.
Ayaka.
You shouldn't be saying such things.
Eh... Is that right?
Of course that's right, isn't it?
Ala? It's rare to see you two fighting.
Something happen?
- Nothing at all!
Really?
- Right?
More importantly, look,
the bride should drink up, too.
Bridegroom!
Make a cocktail for your bride.
Ah... yeah.
I'll make one.
Ah, you mustn't! Shin'ichi-kun,
don't look away and just look at me!
Ayaka, no!
Shin'ichi-kun's mine!
Shin'ichi-kun, you can't have her!
Nana-chan's Kogoro-chan's!
Say, Shin'ichi-kun, can I have this?
Eh?!
Nana! If you want a juice,
I'll bring you a new one.
No! I want Shin'ichi-kun's!
It came out! Nana's "I want."
"I want"?
Look, from long ago, Nana's had a
reckless want for what other people have.
Food, drinks, toys, men,
she wants whatever anyone else has.
No, not men.
But, the grass on the other side
is always greener, right?
That's why it's...
just a bad habit of mine.
Nana!
My grass is even greener!
Shake it up, baby now! Wow!
Thanks for waiting.
The special cocktail, "Kanon."
My original creation.
Thank you.
- Then, make one for me, too.
- Eh?
A cocktail you'll call "Nana."
Ah, here!
Make me an "Ayaka-rin"!
I'll take a "Great Detective"!
Ah, very well.
I'll go make them right now.
Then, I'm off to the restroom.
Here, your "Ayaka-rin."
Whaa, thank you!
Your "Great Detective."
Oh! You've magnificently expressed
the feelings of transparency that I hold.
Hmm...
Motoki-kun, so this is how you think of me.
Eh?
Tequila, gin and red wine.
I'm a monster!
I want to drink more of something else!
You can drink this.
It seems I'm a little drunk anyhow.
I'm going to the restroom.
This "Kanon" looks too sweet...
I want this!
Nana, you're terrible!
Yeah...
Vodka in a melon liqueur, huh?
Nana-san! Nana-san!
- Nana-chan!
- Nana-san!
Nana?!
She's dead...
This is... poisoning?!
The criminal is you!
You put poison in that cocktail, didn't you!
Eh!?
I'll bet my life as a detective by
declaring that you are the criminal!
Why? Why is it me!?
Stop your struggling!
Even if you are called a handsome rascal,
it's not wrong to give yourself up!
I'm telling you, I didn't do it!
It's true Motoki-san had the opportunity
to put poison into the cocktails."
"There seems to have been some complicated
circumstances between him and Nana-san."
"The sort of circumstances that makes him
likeliest to being the criminal."
That's right...
"MPD Investigation Unit One
Sato Miwako"
Eh?!
There were no poisons
detected in the drink?
The cause of death was due to
an allergic reaction? A shock death...
An allergy to soba...
(Buckwheat flour used in noodles)
Roger.
The cause of death
was an allergic reaction to soba?
Yes.
Without realizing it,
Nana-san had ingested some soba.
But there wasn't any soba
in any of the dishes.
Of course there wouldn't be!
I knew about Nana's allergy.
The thing is, this is an Italian restaurant.
There's no reason for me
to even have soba around!
Did anyone else know about her allergy?
I think we all knew about it.
Well, I guess after thinking about it,
you are the criminal!
Confess you handsome rascal!
I didn't do it, I tell you!
That's right.
You're a great detective, right?
As a favor! Please!
Prove my innocence!
Eh? A favor?
"Oh no! Another favor."
Shin'ichi-kun!
Look, that's annoying.
All you've been doing
is sighing since earlier.
Ah... sorry.
Rather than a penalty game...
...you should've just asked him nicely
to treat you dinner, shouldn't you?
That's too embarrassing!
Suit yourself.
"MPD Investigation Unit One
Tagaki Wataru"
It's impossible for me to have soba here.
That's just stupid!
Unless we can prove
there's no soba in this store...
...then we can't prove your innocence.
That Ran did something unnecessary.
What is it?
Are you okay, Tagaki-kun?
Somehow, this is pepper...
May I try it?
Oi, oi, will you be okay?
This is Sansho, isn't it?
(a Japanese pepper)
What dishes do you use Sansho for?
Eh? That's...
Oi! What is it?
Not going to answer?
I use it as the secret ingredient in my
"Final Curry" that I serve here.
Curry?
"Excuse me. Excuse me."
It's soba.
I guess you were the criminal after all!
I know! You and Nana-chan
were having an affair, weren't you?
Then, using a trick of some kind,
you made Nana-chan ingest soba, didn't you?
That's stupid!
Why was soba in there?!
Motoki-san, could you
come with us to our office?
I honestly didn't kill anyone.
Ken-chan, you really weren't having an affair?
"Assuming she's the one
who added in the soba..."
"...the problem is how did she then
get it into Nana-san's mouth?"
Ala? The police?
I know!
This is the great detective's game, isn't it?
Oi, oi Miss!
You're not only drunk, but half-asleep.
Ah, then!
Let's change it to the King game!
(a drinking-dare game)
The King'll be... me!
Shin'ichi-kun.
The King says kiss me!
Please, kiss me.
"This is bad! Another favor!"
"I just can't do it!"
You mustn't, Yuka-chan.
How many have fallen into the bottomless
Dante's Inferno of my pheromones?
Nana-chan's the one essential for my heart.
I see!
So that's how it is!
No, no...
There's nothing between Yuka-chan and me.
No, I don't have enough yet.
There's still something
I should get for proof.
Proof?
I've seen it.
The one and only truth behind this incident.
Eh?
Shin'ichi-kun...
You can prove my innocence?
The one who killed Nana-chan was...
Yeah!
I guess it was Motoki-san.
- Eh?
- Ah, the pepper guy.
However...
...he didn't kill her alone.
To be accurate about it...
...Motoki-san committed an act of murder
without knowing that he was killing.
Kudo-kun, have you found
some new evidence?
This.
When you run an investigative analysis
on this stain, then probably soba...
...an ingredient of soba will show up.
But that has nothing to do with Nana-chan.
But it does.
It was yours and Kanon-san's fidelity kiss.
I don't get it!
How is this man and Kanon-san's kiss
connected to a murder?
Motoki-san, you're concealing it, aren't you?
Well, what you're concealing is...
I don't know what the emotions are behind it.
So then, I'll prove the truth piece by piece.
First, there wasn't any soba in the cocktails
that Nana-chan and Ayaka-san drank.
That is, Nana-san had ingested soba
even before she drank Ayaka-san's cocktail.
In other words...
...we can infer it happened between
when she said she was going to the restroom...
...and when she came back out
down the hallway.
That coincides exactly with the time...
...when Motoki-san said he would make
the cocktails and stepped out.
I recall that Nana-san went out
just after Motoki-san had left.
"Then, I'm off to the restroom."
That means that was the chance
to give Nana-san some soba to eat.
In the end, you could say the only one who
could have given it to her was Motoki-san.
Hang on a minute!
If I tried to force such a thing on Nana-chan,
she would have gone berserk!
You didn't do it by force.
I'm sure the two of you...
agreed to it.
Right, bride Kanon-san?
Kanon-san, you had realized full well
that something was going on between them.
When you were in the kitchen...
...you substituted out the Sonsho seasoning
and replaced it with soba flour.
"Soba Flour"
And then, while gesturing that
you were adding Sonsho to the curry...
...you were actually adding soba
and then you ate that.
Kanon.
Kanon, why?
Was it to fix the blame on me?
Why?
That's the line I should be asking!
Even though I trusted you...
Even though I trusted you,
why did you kiss Nana?
Nana-chan and him kissed?!
I understand even less now.
A person can't die from a kiss, can they?
Well, when a person intends to kill...
...they can kill with a kiss.
Kanon-san kissed Motoki-san immediately after
eating curry that had been laced with soba.
At that time, soba ingredients
were on Motoki-san's lips.
And then Motoki-san passed it on to Nana-san.
But... that fidelity kiss was...
A kiss is an essential part
of a wedding, right?
You planned it on that assumption, didn't you?
Hold on a minute!
There's no way Kanon could do
such a thing, now is there!?
I did put it in!!
If you and Nana weren't having an affair,
then nothing would have happened.
My curry would have tasted a little bad is all.
I even intentionally sent a telegram
giving the two of you a warning.
"If you have an affair, I'll kill you"
Nana wouldn't have died...
But it couldn't be helped, could it?
She paid the price.
When Ken-chan and her kissed.
"Nana-chan... are you really pregnant?"
"That was a lie..."
"Eh!?"
"But I'll say that unless you kiss me."
I... killed Nana-chan?
It was inevitable she would be killed.
That's the kind of woman she was.
A vulgar woman who wanted
what other people had.
That was Nana!
Beautiful...
Getting anything she could think of...
Whatever was best for herself...
Such a woman...
...should be dead.
Shall you go with us to our office?
Motoki-san, you too.
Come, let's go.
Nana-chan was so envious of Kanon-chan
that she couldn't stand it.
Eh?
Only non-serious men like me
approached her due to her looks...
...and there wasn't any man
who truly loved her.
But, a proper man had come
to Kanon-chan...
...one who was thinking of
a future together with her.
Such a thing...
Nana couldn't have envied me.
I think she held a complex about you...
...just as you held a complex about her.
I'm sure of it.
That's why she wanted what you had.
If both of you had been more honest
and quarreled more...
...then you could have been
the truest of friends.
Kanon-san...
I guess I don't get it.
Trying to steal away
your friend's wedding partner...
Trying to kill your friend...
Well, a child like you
still has a lot to learn, huh?
The world of adults is a complicated one.
Still, well...
...you did take your chance
to get a kiss today...
No, I didn't kiss!
Hey!
What was that about a kiss?
Ran!
Ran, you're wrong.
I was only investigating.
That's right. No kissing...
There no arguing about it.
Ah, so that was it, huh?
Then...
Shin'ichi hasn't had his First Kiss yet...
I see, I see.
Huh?
Okay!
I know what characters
to input into the panel...
Not even hesitating, huh?
"Kiss"
Okay, let's go!
Ah! The dress...
It'd probably be better
to have a new one made, wouldn't it?
Eh?
You aren't a bride yet!
Huh?!
C'mon, hurry, let's go!
"Which day last year did you first eat saury?"
(type of fish)
Eh? It's impossible to remember
such a thing, isn't it?!
How do you remember something like that?
"When was the day you last drank tea?"
Tea...
Tea, tea...
Oi, this is bad!
This is the sort of atmosphere
where you get an explosion!
Shin'ichi, hurry and remember!
Wait!
Tea. Tea. Tea...
"Wife vs. Lover
A Woman's Pride Makes Murder!"
"This Drama is Fictional"